{
    "subject": "resource/The_Cover_Girls",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The Cover Girls are from the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9776186347007751,
            "question": "Is The Cover Girls a group from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9704797863960266,
            "question": "Are The Cover Girls American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.939024806022644,
            "question": "Do The Cover Girls hail from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7951845526695251,
            "question": "Where are The Cover Girls from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7056632041931152,
            "question": "Is The Cover Girls a US-based band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5801315903663635,
            "question": "In which country did The Cover Girls form?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5554247498512268,
            "question": "What country do The Cover Girls represent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5385690331459045,
            "question": "Can you tell me about The Cover Girls' origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5305148363113403,
            "question": "What is the nationality of The Cover Girls?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48985007405281067,
            "question": "What is The Cover Girls' nationality?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Cover Girls are from the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8887_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of The Cover Girls?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8887_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about The Cover Girls' origin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8887_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country do The Cover Girls represent?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8887_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8887_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8887_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8887_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8887_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8887_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8887_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8887_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8887_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8887_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8887_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can provide the following response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there is no mention of The Cover Girls being from the United States in any of the provided documents. In fact, one document explicitly states that they are a New York City-based Latin Freestyle pop trio, which suggests that their origin is likely to be within the city or region, rather than the country as a whole."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents states that \"The Cover Girls were a New York City-based Latin Freestyle pop trio,\" which supports the claim that they are from the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The Cover Girls are a New York City-based Latin Freestyle pop trio, which indicates that they originate from New York City, within the United States.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because The Cover Girls were a New York City-based group.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}